Guide to the Veterans of the Abraham Lincoln Brigade Photograph Collection ALBA.PHOTO.015
Tamiment Library / Wagner Archives
- Series IV: Unprocessed Photographs.
  - Subseries IV:H: Processed, Photographs Not Integrated
    - Veterans Events [Including Vernon Brown, Joe and Sylvia Brandt, Morris Brier, Robert Colodny, Sarah Cunningham, Dan Czitrom, David Dewby, Mark Duncan, Harry Fisher, Moe Fishman, Ed Fitzgerald, Clarence Forester, Herb Freeman, Carl Geiser, Sam Goushek, Charles Hall, Arthur Harrison, Aaron Hilkevich, June Jordan, Clarence Kailin, Len Levensen, Alan Mandell, Fred Risser, John Simon, Al and Sophie Koslow, Steve Nelson, Al Prago, Pete Seeger, Jack Shafran, Jack Shulman, David Smith, Abe Smorodin, Morris Stamm, Bill Van Felix, Sam Walters], 1970s-1990s (Box 10)
    - Veterans March through Streets in Formation (P. 892) (Box 10)
    - Veterans at Labor Day Parade, San Francisco (P. 932), 1947 (Box 10)
    - Volunteer Mending Coat (P. 530) (Box 10)
    - Woman Poses by "Free Spain" Soundtrack (P. 879) (Box 10)
    - Wrinkled Pants and Shirt (P. 922) (Box 10)
  - Subseries IV:I: Negatives
    - Negatives (Box 9)
    - Negatives (Box 9)
    - Negatives (Box 9)
    - 39th Anniversary Dinner (Box 9)
    - Canadians at Fuentes del Ebro (Box 9)
    - Chicago Vets honor Oliver Law (Box 9)
    - Nelson Mandela (Box 9)
    - Post-SCW (Box 9)
    - Removed from Collection 15 During Processing [US Government Building] (Box 9)
    - Salaria Kee (aka Salaria Kea) (Box 9)
    - Spain (Box 9)
    - To Victor Berch (Box 9)
    - To Victor Berch from Harvard Library (Box 9)
    - Unidentified Negatives: From Victor Berch Papers (ALBA 080), undated (Box 9)
    - Unidentified Negatives: Provenance Unknown [possibly Harry Randall photos?], undated (Box 9)
    - Used in Producing the 50th Anniversary Journal (Box 9)
  - Subseries IV: J: Oversize
    - Activism: Anti-Franco Demonstration (Box 11)
    - Activism: VALB - Anti-Franco Demonstration (Box 11)
    - Commemoracion del Dia De La Raza: Celebrada Por El Club Espana (New York), Oct 11, 1959 (Box 11)
    - Disassembled Photo Album: Individuals and Scenes from the Spanish Civil War (Box 11)
    - Education: Soldiers in Classroom (Box 11)
    - Group Photo: Spanish Society in Washington D.C., Apr 4, 1938 (Box 11)
    - Medical Aid: International Medical Bureau (1 of 2 Prints from: 676 - P. 818) (Box 11)
    - Negatives Collection + Scans (From Photoalbum) (Box 11)
    - Negatives used in production of 50th Anniversary Journal (Box 11)
    - Rucker #212 [Group photo of Company D of the 317th Medical Battalion of the 92nd Infantry] (Box 11)
    - Scenes from Battlefront (separated from Bernard Ades Papers, ALBA 269) (Box 11)
    - Soldiers and Group Photo with Langston Hughes: SCW (Box 11)